<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City</string>

    <string name="nairobi_national_park">Nairobi National Park</string>
    <string name="nairobi_national_park_description">Highlights: Black Rhino Conservation, Big Five
        Presence,(Read More)Nairobi National Park, located about seven kilometres from downtown
        Nairobi, is the city\'s most famous attraction.It offers an exciting safari experience,where
        visitors can see lions, cheetahs, rhinos, hippos, and giraffes roaming in the dense
        grasslands. What makes it unique is that it's the only national park in the world situated
        within a capital city.

    </string>

    <string name="giraffe_centre">Giraffe Centre</string>
    <string name="giraffe_centre_description">The Giraffe Centre in Nairobi is an environmental
        conservation centre dedicated to protecting the endangered Rothschild\'s giraffe. A visit to
        the Giraffe Centre not only allows you to get up close and personal with Africa's tallest
        mammal but also directly supports the conservation efforts for these majestic creatures.
    </string>

    <string name="national_museum">Nairobi Museum</string>
    <string name="national_museum_description">The Nairobi National Museum, founded in 1929, is an
        important place in Kenya where you can learn about the country\'s four pillars - history,
        culture, and natural heritage. You can explore exhibits and collections that show Kenya's
        diverse identity, including its long history of human civilization and the amazing wildlife
        and landscapes found here.
    </string>

    <string name="karen_blixen_museum">Karen Blixen Museum</string>
    <string name="karen_blixen_museum_description">The Karen Blixen Museum, located about ten
        kilometres from downtown Nairobi, was once the home of the famous Danish author Karen Blixen.
        Opened in 1985 to remember her life and work, the museum displays collections that reflect
        the time she spent in Kenya, giving visitors insight into her fascinating life and the
        historical period she lived in.
    </string>

    <string name="david_sheldrick_wildlife_trust">David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust</string>
    <string name="david_sheldrick_wildlife_trust_description">The David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust,
        located in Nairobi National Park, is a well-known nonprofit organisation that rescues and
        helps elephants, rhinos, and other animals in Kenya. They take care of orphaned baby
        elephants that have been hurt by poaching, drought, or conflicts with people. Visitors can
        watch these baby elephants being fed, cleaned, and playing in mud baths.
    </string>

    <string name="bomas_of_kenya">Bomas of Kenya</string>
    <string name="bomas_of_kenya_description">Bomas of Kenya is a tourist village tour in Nairobi,
        offering a glimpse into the traditional villages of Kenya\'s tribes. Through exhibits,
        visitors learn about each tribe's way of life, including their social structure, music, and
        dance, providing an enriching cultural experience.
    </string>

    <string name="village_market">Village Market</string>
    <string name="village_market_description">Nairobi Village Market is the largest entertainment
        and shopping outlet in East Africa, located in the Gigiri residential area. It is designed
        to resemble an African market in the open, with waterfalls, rivers, plants and gardens
        dotting the complex.

    </string><string name="railway_museum">Railway Museum</string>
    <string name="railway_museum_description">Built in 1971, the world-famous Nairobi Railway Museum
        is a spectacular landmark promising to protect and showcase the precious antique records of
        the railways of East Africa. The museum has many galleries displaying the age-old
        collections of local trains.

    </string><string name="maasai_market">Maasai Market</string>
    <string name="maasai_market_description">Widely popular and extremely recommended by every local
        , Masaai market is a must-visit for handicraft shoppers. This is a vibrant open-air market
        in multiple locations in Nairobi where visitors can shop for authentic African crafts,
        jewellery, and souvenirs. From historic African paintings to amazing handicrafts, this
        endless market is all the more attractive because of its cheap rates.

    </string>

    <string name="karura_forest">Karura Forest</string>
    <string name="karura_forest_description">The urban gazetted Karura forest is located in Nairobi,
        Kenya, and is abundant with natural beauty and resources. It is divided into three parts by
        Limuru and Kiambu roads. The forest has a natural trail running up to 50 km that facilitates
        visitors to walk, run, and bike around the forest. One can also rent a trail bike.
    </string>

    <string name="uhuru_gardens_memorial">Uhuru Gardens</string>
    <string name="uhuru_gardens_memorial_description">Uhuru Gardens is Kenya\'s largest urban
        commemorative and memorial park, located along Langata Road, Nairobi. It was established to
        celebrate the country’s independence from the British Empire in 1963 and was declared a
        National Monument in 1966. It houses three historically significant monuments that draw the
        attention of tourists
    </string>

    <string name="two_rivers_mall">The Two Rivers Mall</string>
    <string name="two_rivers_mall_description">The Two Rivers Mall is the largest shopping centre in
        Sub-Saharan Africa, located on Limuru Road in Ruaka, Nairobi. It houses over 20 local and
        international brands and 200 stores. The dancing fountains here are spectacular, especially
        when lit up at night. Africa’s tallest Ferris wheel, the Eye of Kenya, is also located here.

    </string><string name="the_hub_karen">The Hub Karen</string>
    <string name="the_hub_karen_description">The Hub Karen is a massive mall and entertainment
        centre in the Karen suburb of Nairobi. It has more than 85 stores selling clothing, footwear,
        accessories, pet products, toys, sports goods, electronics, beauty and skincare products,
        homeware items, etc. Fun activities like ziplining and airbag jumping are available here too.
    </string>
    <string name="snake_park">Snake Park</string>
    <string name="snake_park_description">Situated near Nairobi National Museum, the Snake Park
        showcases a variety of Kenyan snake species and other reptiles. Visitors can learn about
        these creatures through guided tours. The park is accessible by road, and a visit here
        typically takes 1-2 hours.
    </string>

    <string name="kenyatta_international_conference">Kenyatta International Conference
    Centre</string>
    <string name="kenyatta_international_conference_description">Kenyatta International Conference
        Centre, situated in the heart of Nairobi, is a renowned landmark is best known for holding
        official gatherings, meetings and conferences. Visitors can marvel at its impressive
        architecture and panoramic views from the rooftop helipad, accessible during business hours.
    </string>

    <string name="african_heritage_house">African Heritage House</string>
    <string name="african_heritage_house_description">A National Monument and museum, the African
        Heritage House is situated in front of the Nairobi National Park in Mlolongo. Within the
        house are artefacts, artworks, jewellery, textiles, traditional pottery, weapons, antiques,
        ceremonial clothes and more. It is open for tours, lunches or dinners and overnight stays.
    </string>

    <string name="arboretum">Nairobi Arboretum</string>
    <string name="arboretum_description">Nairobi Arboretum is 30.4 acres of a wooded paradise home
        to over 350 species of indigenous and exotic plant life and over 100 species of birds. It is
        located along the State House Road in Kilimani. It has shaded trails for walkways, picnic
        lawns and jogging trails. Sykes and Vervet monkeys can also be spotted here.
    </string>

    <string name="ngong_road_forest_sanctuary">Ngong Road Forest Sanctuary</string>
    <string name="ngong_road_forest_sanctuary_description">Ngong Road Forest Sanctuary is a managed
        forest on the outskirts of Nairobi in Jamhuri. It is a popular place to explore the flora of
        Kenya and go for a quick run or walk Bushbucks, civets, porcupines, pythons, green snakes,
        puddle frogs, and many more animals can be spotted here. Roughly 113 bird species exist
        within the forest, including African Harrier Hawk and Narina trogons.
    </string>

    <string name="nairobi_central_park">The Central Park of Nairobi</string>
    <string name="nairobi_central_park_description">The Central Park of Nairobi is a public park
        situated behind Nairobi Serena Hotel and adjacent to the famous Uhuru Park. Nyayo monument,
        dedicated to Kenya’s second president, Daniel Toroitich Arap Moi, is a major landmark within
        the park for tourists and photographers. It is also a popular picnic spot and boasts a
        children’s playground.
    </string>

    <string name="go_kart">GP Karting</string>
    <string name="go_kart_description">Outside Nairobi town, we arrived at GP Karting. Our clients
        were taught on how to drive the Karts, given the first lap to first master how to manuever
        through the corners while karting, then after left to race together.
        The staff was so welcoming, and we hope to be back there soon!
    </string>

    <string name="mercardo_restaurant">Mercardo Restaurant</string>
    <string name="mercardo_restaurant_description">Exquisitely presented and beautifully balanced,
        the menu at Mercado is fun, flavorful and simply fantastic. The rustic environment with
        wooden swing seating, bold colors and lit market baskets create the perfect atmosphere to
        entertain. The terrace overlooking the city is famous for its sundowners and happy hours
        with the award-winning cocktail menu.
    </string>

    <string name="animal_orphanage">Animal Orphanage</string>
    <string name="animal_orphanage_description">Nairobi Animal Orphanage is a wildlife
        rehabilitation centre in Nairobi National Park. It is the oldest of its kind in Kenya.
        Hyenas, leopards and scarce Sokoke cats are some wildlife that can be found here. Various
        birds can also be viewed, including parrots, guinea fowls, crowned cranes and ostriches.
    </string>

    <string name="ngong_hills">Ngong Hills</string>
    <string name="ngong_hills_description">Ngong Hills, near Nairobi, Kenya, are a famous set of
        peaks known for their stunning views and cultural significance. Rising sharply from the
        plains, these hills became well-known through Karen Blixen's book and movie "Out of Africa."
        Standing at around 2,460 meters tall, they offer amazing views of the Rift Valley and
        Nairobi
    </string>

    <string name="nairobi_gallery">Nairobi Gallery</string>
    <string name="nairobi_gallery_description">Situated on Kenyatta Avenue in Nairobi, the Nairobi
        Gallery is a museum showcasing African art. It is housed within a National Monument
        established in the early 20th century on the site of the old Provisional Commissioner's
        office. It is also the site of Point Zero, from which all distances used to be measured in
        Israel.
    </string>

    <string name="lavington_mall">Lavington Mall</string>
    <string name="lavington_mall_description">Lavington Mall is one of the largest shopping malls
        in Nairobi, located along the James Gichuru Road within the Lavington Green shopping area.
        It is the ideal destination for shopping, dining and other fun activities. It is filled with
        quaint bakeries and diners, pocket friendly apparel stores and pampering skin and haircare
        locations.
    </string>

    <string name="uhuru_park">Uhuru Park</string>
    <string name="uhuru_park_description">Uhuru Park is a 13-hectare residential park located on
        Uhuru Highway, across from Nairobi InterContinental Hotel. It is equipped with an artificial
        lake, a fountain and an assembly ground perfect for skateboarding. It also houses the Nyayo
        monument and offers great views of the city’s skyline. Boating, horse and camel riding, and
        remote control mobile cars are popular activities here.
    </string>

    <string name="oloolua_nature_trail">Oloolua Nature Trail</string>
    <string name="oloolua_nature_trail_description">The Oloolua Nature Trail is a 5km natural trail
        in the tropical Oloolua Forest of the Karen neighbourhood. The trail is popular for jogging,
        walking, picnicking amidst stunning forest views, and hiking. Many indigenous trees and
        plants can be found here. A 20-foot waterfall at the forest entrance is the highlight, along
        with a campsite equipped with bonfire facilities.
    </string>

    <string name="fair_view">Fair View</string>
    <string name="fair_view_description">The secret of Nairobi\'s Upper Hill, that is the Fairview
        Hotel. It\'s the tranquillity created by our lush gardens, tapestry of pathways and those
        little surprises around each corner that travelers tell us makes them fall in love with the
        Fairview Hotel. Our hotel offers a wide range of different bedrooms; from rooms within the
        gardens to Manor House suites, a choice that enables travelers to return to the Fairview
        whenever leisure or business brings them back to Nairobi.
        Karibu! - Welcome
    </string>

    <string name="villa_rossa_kempinski">Villa Rossa Kempinski</string>
    <string name="villa_rossa_kempinski_description">Looking for a place to stay in Nairobi? Then
        look no further than Villa Rosa Kempinski Nairobi, a family-friendly hotel that brings the
        best of Nairobi to your doorstep. Guest rooms offer a flat screen TV, air conditioning, and
        a minibar, and Villa Rosa Kempinski Nairobi makes getting online easy as free wifi is
        available. You can also take advantage of some of the amenities offered by the hotel,
        including a rooftop terrace, a concierge, and room service. In addition, guests can enjoy a
        pool and free breakfast during their visit.
    </string>

    <string name="cjs">CJs</string>
    <string name="cjs_description">CJ’s, a fully fledged restaurant specializing in delivering a
        relaxed and memorable dining experience. Each location features a unique ambience with
        tasteful decor, specially designed for your comfort. To make you feel more at home, we’ve
        carefully selected a unique theme for each location.
    </string>

    <string name="radisson_blue">Radisson Blu Hotel</string>
    <string name="radisson_blue_description">Located just 20 minutes\' drive from both Nairobi
        National Park and the airport, the Radisson Blu Hotel - a five star hotel - in the heart of
        the fast-growing business district of Upper Hill is the perfect base for a Business Trip or
        Kenyan Safari. Our 271 luxurious rooms and suites come complete with free Wi-Fi, a minibar,
        along with lovely city or park views, offering you the best value for money.
    </string>

    <string name="nairobi_default">Nairobi City</string>
    <string name="nairobi_default_description">Nairobi is Kenya’s capital city. In addition to its
        urban core, the city has Nairobi National Park, a large game reserve known for breeding
        endangered black rhinos and home to giraffes, zebras and lions. Next to it is a
        well-regarded elephant orphanage operated by the David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust. Nairobi is
        also often used as a jumping-off point for safari trips elsewhere in Kenya.
    </string>

</resources>