<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Uplift</string>
    <string name="day_number">"Day %d "</string>
    <string name="one">There is no fear in love. But perfect love drives out fear, because fear has to do with punishment.</string>
    <string name="two">" But even if you should suffer for what is right, you are blessed. “Do not fear their threats ; do not be frightened.”"</string>
    <string name="three">For the Spirit God gave us does not make us timid, but gives us power, love and self-discipline.</string>
    <string name="four">" say to those with fearful hearts, “Be strong, do not fear; your God will come, he will come with vengeance; with divine retribution he will come to save you.”"</string>
    <string name="five">" but those who hope in the LORD will renew their strength. They will soar on wings like eagles; they will run and not grow weary, they will walk and not be faint."</string>
    <string name="six">" So do not fear, for I am with you; do not be dismayed, for I am your God. I will strengthen you and help you; I will uphold you with my righteous right hand."</string>
    <string name="seven">Now faith is confidence in what we hope for and assurance about what we do not see.</string>
    <string name="eight">Have I not commanded you? Be strong and courageous. Do not be afraid; do not be discouraged, for the LORD your God will be with you wherever you go.”</string>
    <string name="nine">Therefore I tell you, do not worry about your life, what you will eat or drink; or about your body, what you will wear. Is not life more than food, and the body more than clothes?</string>
    <string name="ten">I sought the LORD, and he answered me; he delivered me from all my fears.I sought the LORD, and he answered me; he delivered me from all my fears.</string>
    <string name="eleven">The righteous cry out, and the LORD hears them; he delivers them from all their troubles.</string>
    <string name="twelve">For I am convinced that neither death nor life, neither angels nor demons, neither the present nor the future, nor any powers, neither height nor depth, nor anything else in all creation, will be able to separate us from the love of God that is in Christ Jesus our Lord.</string>
    <string name="thirteen">Trust in the LORD with all your heart and lean not on your own understanding; in all your ways submit to him, and he will make your paths straight.</string>
    <string name="fourteen">But blessed is the one who trusts in the LORD, whose confidence is in him.</string>
    <string name="fifteen">The angel answered, “The Holy Spirit will come on you, and the power of the Most High will overshadow you. So the holy one to be born will be called the Son of God. For no word from God will ever fail.”</string>
    <string name="sixteen">Do not be anxious about anything, but in every situation, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God. And the peace of God, which transcends all understanding, will guard your hearts and your minds in Christ Jesus.</string>
    <string name="seventeen">Do not be afraid, little flock, for your Father has been pleased to give you the kingdom. Sell your possessions and give to the poor. Provide purses for yourselves that will not wear out, a treasure in heaven that will never fail, where no thief comes near and no moth destroys. For where your treasure is, there your heart will be also.</string>
    <string name="eighteen">Come to me, all you who are weary and burdened, and I will give you rest.</string>
    <string name="nineteen">The LORD is my shepherd, I lack nothing.\n</string>
    <string name="twenty_one">" Peace I leave with you; my peace I give you. I do not give to you as the world gives. Do not let your hearts be troubled and do not be afraid."</string>
    <string name="twenty_two">Let the peace of Christ rule in your hearts, since as members of one body you were called to peace. And be thankful.</string>
    <string name="twenty_three">Now may the Lord of peace himself give you peace at all times and in every way. The Lord be with all of you.</string>
    <string name="twenty_four">Cast your cares on the LORD and he will sustain you; he will never let the righteous be shaken.</string>
    <string name="twenty_five">" Anxiety weighs down the heart, but a kind word cheers it up."</string>
    <string name="twenty_six">Humble yourselves, therefore, under God’s mighty hand, that he may lift you up in due time. Cast all your anxiety on him because he cares for you.</string>
    <string name="twenty_seven">Even though I walk through the darkest valley,I will fear no evil, for you are with me; your rod and your staff, they comfort me.</string>
    <string name="twenty_eight">" Keep your lives free from the love of money and be content with what you have, because God has said, “Never will I leave you; never will I forsake you.” So we say with confidence, “The Lord is my helper; I will not be afraid. What can mere mortals do to me?”"</string>
    <string name="twenty_nine">When anxiety was great within me, your consolation brought me joy</string>
    <string name="thirty">The LORD will vindicate me; your love, LORD, endures forever— do not abandon the works of your hands.</string>
    <string name="twenty">But seek first his kingdom and his righteousness, and all these things will be given to you as well.</string>
</resources>